http://www.plattco.com/privacy-statement

englishEspañolDeutschefrançaisProductsPlattco DOUBLE FLAP AIRLOCK VALVESLIDE / ISOLATION GATESCustom High Temp / Pressure Slide GatesRotary Valve replacement optionsSafety EnhancementsPerformance EnhancementsEasy Maintenance TechnologyMechanical Shaft SealCustom CastingsServicesabout Our ServicesField Service & RepairRebuild ProgramReplacement parts40+ Point ValVe InspectionCollaborative Engineering& Design ServicesMObile Demonstration UnitFree-Trial ProgramRegrind ProgramIndustriesSuccessSuccess Storiesintegrys CASE STUDYlincolnway energy CASE STUDYNucor CASE STUDYPonderay CASE STUDYWilkes-barre CASE STUDYResourcesPrintable ProductSheets & ManualsVideosapply for creditCompanyAbout PlattcoQuality AssuranceMeet the StaffSales TerritoriesEmployment OpportunitiesThe Story of Plattco’s Hessian Soldier LogoCommunity InvolvementIn the newsQuoteValve QuoteSlide Gate quoteField Service QuoteContactLanguageEspanolDEUTSCHEFRANÇAISEnglishPrivacy StatementThis website and its content, which may be modified from time to time, are subject to a Legal Disclaimer, Trademark and Copyright Notice, and a Privacy Statement and maintained for the purpose of providing public access to information about Plattco and our products.If you do not fully agree with these legal notices and their intent, please do not use this website.If you do not fully agree with these legal notices and their intent, please do not use this website.Please note that the World Wide Web is a publicly accessible system. Making personal information voluntarily available online is done at your own risk.Whereas Plattco appreciates your interest in this website and respects your privacy, Plattco also recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal data which may be collected when visiting our website. While such information is processed according to the legal provisions of the United States of America (where this website is maintained), this website may include, however, links to third party websites which are not covered by this privacy statement and for which Plattco has no responsibility or liability.Plattco collects personal data only when voluntarily submitted by visitors. Such data is used for internal purposes stated at the location where provided – for example, when requesting a quote, contact by a sales representative, etc.This is how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website. The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting our site.If you visit our site to read or download information, such as brochures, newsletters or press releases:Plattco may make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity and to collect such information as i.e. browser type and operating system, metrics, geographical location, on an anonymous, aggregate basis, in order to tailor information to suit your individual preferences. We do not store any personal identifiers. This information is not stored in any particular fashion, but is part of a systems log file.For site management, information is collected for statistical purposes. Our system utilizes software programs that create summary statistics, which are then used for such purposes as assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. This information is only used internally, does not contain personal identifiers, and will only be used for internal management purposes.If you identify yourself by sending an E-mail, filling out a registration form, or questionnaire:You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail (e-mail) message. We use personally identifying information from consumers in various ways to further our customer's protection and to provide better service. This may be to correct broken links that you have identified or provide additional information that you have requested. See Talk to Us to learn what can happen to the information you provide us when you send us e-mail or fill out an information request form. Any information that we collect via a registration form or questionnaire may be subject to disclosure, but will be handled in accordance with the requirements of the Privacy Act and the Freedom of Information Act to ensure the greatest protection of personal privacy in the face of any required disclosure.We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us.LInksBe aware that the sites you may link to from our web pages may collect information from you, and the practices of those web sites, use of cookies etc., are not covered under this disclosure. We advocate that you read their privacy disclosures in order to be further aware of what information is collected about you and how it is used.If you have any questions or comments about the information presented here, please contact us using the subject line “Website Privacy” at:Plattco Corporation7 White StreetPlattsburgh, NY 12901(518) 563-4640info@plattco.comTalk to UsYou can contact us by regular mail, telephone, or electronic mail. You may fill out a registration form or questionnaire. Before you do, there are a few things you should know.Various people may see the material you submit. We may enter the information you send into our electronic contact database. This information may be used to determine how to better serve our customers or obtain feedback on services you’d like to see us provide, how we are doing, or obtain comments. This information will not be sold to any other organization.Any information that we collect via a request form or other electronic submission may be subject to disclosure, but will be handled in accordance with the requirements of the Privacy Act and the Freedom of Information Act to ensure the greatest protection of personal privacy in the face of any required disclosure.Also, e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is very sensitive, or includes personal information like your bank account, credit card, or social security number, you might want to send it by postal mail instead.People under the age of 18 are advised to get permission from a parent or guardian before submitting personally identifiable data to Plattco websites.Copyright © 2007-2017 Plattco Corporation, Plattsburgh, New York. All rights reserved.When your process is critical, when conditions are demanding, when your valve has to work, it has to be a Plattco Valve.EMAIL: info@plattco.comPhone: +1.518.563.4640Fax: 1.518.563.48927 White Street, Plattsburgh, NY 12901 legal Disclaimer |  privacy statement  |  trademark & copyright
